It’s your birthright as a human being to become the Spirit.
Это ваше право с рождения как человеческого существа стать Духом.
That is what Sahaja Yoga is – Saha means “with” and ja is “born."
Это то чем явялятся Сахаджа Йога. "Саха" означает "С" и "джа" рождённое
Born with you is the right to get this yoga, is the union with the divine.
Рождённое с вами это право получить эту Йогу, этот союз с Божественным.
It’s your birthright as a human being.
Это ваше право с рождения как человеческого существа.
You are as I told you at the epitome of evolution.
Как Я сказала , вы эпитома эволюции
And it has to work out, but please open your hearts and open your minds.
И все должно получиться, но, пожалуйста, откройте свои сердца и откройте свои умы.
The unique experience of self-realization
Уникальный опыт само-реализации
takes place when the primordial energy called Kundalini is correctly awakened
имеет место, когда первозданная энергия называемая Кундалини пробуждается правильно
by someone who has already experienced and mastered their own self-realization.
кем-то, кто уже имеет такой опыт и хорошо овладел своей само-реализацией.
Shri Mataji has explained that the Kundalini is the power of our spiritual ascent found
Шри Матаджи объясняет, что Кундалини это энергия вашего духовного восхождения
in the triangular bone at the base of the spine called sacrum by the Greeks.
находится в треугольной косточке в основании позвоночника названной Сакрум Греками
It is the power of our pure desire.
И это энергия вашего чистого желания.
When awakened the Kundalini rises spontaneously through six subtle centers called chakras.
Когда Кундалини пробуждается она спонтанно поднимается и проходит шесть тонких центров называемыми чакрами.
The Kundalini then emerges through the fontanelle bone area at the top of thehead
Кундалини выходит через область родничковой кости на верху головы
emitting a cool breeze that can be felt there as well as on the hands.
испускает прохладный ветерок что можно почувствовать также и на ладонях рук